Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004 UA.27.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Houck, Calvin Bryan (Box 131)
- Houck, Calvin Bryan, Trustee (Box 116)
- Hough, Jerry (Box 131)
- Hough, Jerry (Box 78)
- Houpt, Jeffery L. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry, 1997
- Houpt, Jeffrey (Box 28)
- House, James S. (Box 28)
- Howard, Barbara (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Clinical Child Development Unit, Pediatrics
- Howard, D. Robert (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Physician's Program
- Howard, Emma J. (Box 28)
- Howard, J. Woodford (Box 131)
- Howard, J. Woodford (Box 151)
- Howard, J. Woodford (Box 78)
- Howard, J.W. (Box 28)
- Howard, John (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Center for LGBT Life; History
- Howard, Ken (Box 151)
- Howard, Raymond L. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Art and Illustration
- Howard, Raymond L. (Box 131)
- Howard, Steven, Trustee (Box 116)
- Howard, W. Kenneth (Box 28)
- Howard, W. Kenneth (Box 131)
- Howe, Harold, II (Box 28)
- Howe, Harold, II (Box 78)
- Howell, David Noble (Box 78)
- Howell, Doris A. (Box 131)
- Howell, Doris A. (Box 78)
- Howes, Davis Humphrey (Box 78)
- Hoyler, Hamilton M. (Box 151)
- Hoyler, Hamilton M. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Business Auxiliaries
- Hoyler, Hamilton M. (Box 131)
- Hsieh, David (Box 78)
- Huang, Andrew T. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Hematology / Medied Oncology, Medicine
- Huang, Andrew T. (Box 131)
- Hubbell, Jay B. (Box 28)
- Huber, Joel C. (Box 78)
- Huber, Max (Box 28)
- Huber, Max (Box 151)
- Huber, Thomas (Box 28)
- Huckabee, Mary Ellen (Box 151)
- Hudson, Jerry Fitzgerald S., Trustee (Box 116)
- Hudson, William Rucker (Box 131)
- Hudson, William Rucker (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Otolaryngology; Otolaryngology
- Hueckel, Tomasz A. (Box 78)
- Huestis, Charles B. (Box 28)
- Huestis, Charles B. (Box 131)
- Huestis, Charles Benjamin (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Business and Finance, Retired 3/31/1985
- Huetter, Reinhard (Box 78)
- Hughes, Claude LeBernian (Box 78)
- Hughes, George M. (Box 28)
- Hughes, John S. (Box 28)
- Hughes-Schrader, Sally (Box 28)
- Hughes-Schrader, Sally (Box 131)
- Huling, Porter B. (Box 28)
- Hulka, Greg (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Surgery, 2001
- Hull, Alexander (Box 151)
- Hull, Alexander (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: and of Unvergraduate Studies, Romance Languages
- Hull, Alma (Box 131)
- Hull, Alma [Alumnae President 1949] (Box 116)
- Hull, Robert (Box 28)
- Hull, Robert (Box 131)
- Hull, Wayland (Box 28)
- Hull, William N.H. (Box 28)
- Humm, Harold J. (Box 28)
- Humm, Harold J. (Box 131)
- Humphrey, Betty M. (Box 28)
- Humphrey, Don D. (Box 131)
- Humphrey, Don D. (Box 78)
- Humphrey, Don Dougan (Box 28)
- Humphreys, Josephine (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumna; Author
- Humphreys, Margaret (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: History and Medicine
- Humphries, H. W. (Box 78)
- Humphries, H. W. (Box 131)
- Hunt, Alfred M. (Box 131)
- Hunt, Alfred M., Trustee (Box 116)
- Hunt, Joseph M. (Box 112)
- Hunt, Samuel R. (Box 28)
- Hunter, Wanda S. (Box 28)
- Hunter, Wanda Sanborn (Box 131)
- Hunter, Wanda Sanborn (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Zoology, died 4/1990
- Hurd, David (Box 28)
- Hurd, David (Box 131)
- Hurd, David (Box 151)
- Hurlburt, Allan S. (Box 28)
- Hurlburt, Allan S. (Box 151)
- Hurlburt, Allan S. (Box 78)
- Hurley, J. B., Trustee (Box 116)
- Hurwitz, Barrie S. (Box 78)
- Hutcheson, Ann (Box 28)
- Hutcheson, Ann (Box 131)
- Hutson, Harold H. (Box 112)
  Biographical information. Alumnus (1935); President, Greensboro College
- Hyatt, Robert P. (Box 28)
- Hyatt, Robert P. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Religious Life
- Hybels, Celia F. (Box 78)
- Hyde, Henry (Box 112)
- Ideker, Raymond E. (Box 78)
- Iglehart, Dirk (Box 78)
- Ilkow, Peter (Box 28)
- Ingles, Thelma (Box 28)
- Ingram, James M. (Box 28)
- Ingram, James M. & Carol Cox (Box 131)
- Ingram, O. Kelly (Box 28)
- Ingram, O. Kelly (Box 131)
- Ingram, O. Kelly (Box 151)
- Ingram, O. Kelly (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School, Retired 7/1/1988
- Inman, Walker P. [Duke Endowment Trustee, Doris Duke's 1/2 Brother], d. 1954 (Box 116)
- Innis, John Woodson (Box 28)
- Innis, John Woodson (Box 131)
- Irving, William Henry (Box 28)
- Irving, William Henry (Box 131)
- Irving, William Henry (Box 151)
- Isenberg, Sheldon (Box 28)
- Isley, Joseph K. (Box 28)
- Israel, Michael D. (Box 131)
- Israel, Michael D. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Operating Officer, DUMC
- Ivey, George M. (Box 131)
- Ivey, George M., d. 5/1968, Trustee (Box 116)
- Jackon, J. N. (Box 151)
- Jackson, (Mrs.) J.N. (Box 131)
- Jackson, (Mrs.) J.N. (Box 151)
- Jackson, (Mrs.) J.N. (Box 29)
- Jackson, (Retired Security) (Box 151)
- Jackson, David K. (Box 29)
- Jackson, Harry Ross (Box 151)
- Jackson, Harry Ross (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Alumni Publications
- Jackson, Jacquelyne Johnson (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Sociology, Psychiatry and Behavioral Sciences, Effective 3/1/1998; died 1/28/2004
- Jackson, John N. (Box 29)
- Jackson, Richard L. (Box 29)
- Jackson, Richard Long (Box 131)
- Jackson, Robert B. (Box 78)
- Jackson, Robert J.V (Box 29)
- Jackson, Wallace (Box 78)
- Jacobansky, Ann Madeline (Box 78)
- Jacobansky, Ann. (Box 29)
- Jacobansky, Dean (Box 151)
- Jacobs, Miriam J. (Box 29)
- Jacobs, Timothy Lee (Box 78)
- Jaeger, Boi Jon (Box 29)
- Jaeger, Boi Jon (Box 78)
- Jaffe, Stephen (Box 78)
- James, Carl Clifton (Box 29)
- James, Daniel Maddison (Box 78)
- Jameson, Fredric R. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Comparative Lit.; French; Gradied Program in Literature
- Janan, Micaela W. (Box 78)
- Janocraft, A. (Box 29)
- Janoski, Thomas E. (Box 78)
- Jantz, Harold (Box 29)
- Jarboe, Wallace E. (Box 29)
- Jarmul, David (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: News and Communications
- Jarrard, Norman E. (Box 29)
- Jarrett, McRae (Box 78)
- Jarvis, Erich (Box 78)
- Jaszczak, Ronald Jack (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Imaging, Radiology; Biomedical Engineering
- Jayne, Benjamin A. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: and Froestry
- Jefferies, Dwight (Box 29)
- Jeffers, Frances (Box 151)
- Jeffers, Frances C. (Box 29)
- Jeffers, Frances Caroline (Box 78)
- Jeffers, Katharine R. (Box 29)
- Jeffrey, Paul (Box 132)
- Jeffrey, Paul (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Jazz Studies
- Jeffries, Shaver Dakal, Trustee 1996-1999 (Box 116)
- Jeffs, Peter W. (Box 29)
- Jeffs, Peter W. (Box 132)
- Jeffs, Peter Walter (Box 78)
- Jelovsek, Frederick (Box 29)
- Jelovsek, Frederick (Box 132)
- Jenkins, James Lewis (Box 78)
- Jenkins, Kimberly, Trustee (Box 116)
- Jenkins, Marianna (Box 29)
- Jenkins, Marianna (Box 132)
- Jenkins, Marianna (Box 151)
- Jenkins, Robert M. (Box 29)
- Jenkins, Robert M. (Box 132)
- Jenkins, Robert M. (Box 151)
- Jenks, Alan W. (Box 29)
- Jenks, Alan W. (Box 151)
- Jenks, Alan W. (Box 132)
- Jennings, Edward M., III (Box 78)
- Jennings, Ralph E. (Box 29)
- Jennings, Ralph Edmond (Box 78)
- Jennings, Robert Burgess (Box 78)
- Jennings, William Beatty, Jr. (Box 78)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Loyalty Fund Programs
- Jensen, Douglas Reid (Box 151)
- Jensen, Douglas Reid (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Student Union
- Jensen, Howard E. (Box 29)
- Jensen, Nancy (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: News and Communications, DUMC
- Jensen, Wallace W. (Box 29)
- Jentleson, Bruce W. (Box 79)
- Jewell, Malcolm E. (Box 29)
- Jewell, Malcolm E. (Box 132)
- Jewett, Paul H. (Box 29)
- Jezierski, Bronislas de Leval (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Slavic Languages and Literature, died 6/11/2000
- Jiang, Wei, 2001 (Box 79)
- Jiminez, John P. (Box 29)
- Jirtle, Randy Lynn (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiation and Molecular Oncology Research, DUMC
- Jobe, James K. (Box 29)
- Jobe, James K. (Box 132)
- Jobsis, Frans Frederik (Box 79)
- Joerg, Frederick Charles (Box 29)
- Joerg, Frederick Charles (Box 132)
- Joerg, Frederick Charles (Box 79)
- John, Ralph C. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus (School); President, Simpson College
- Johns, Christa T. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Germanic Lang. and Lit.; Summer Session
- Johns, Sheridan W., III (Box 79)
- Johnsen, Thomas N., Jr. (Box 29)
- Johnson, Carter Charles (Box 79)
- Johnson, Charles (Box 132)
- Johnson, Charles Buchanan (Box 132)
- Johnson, Charles Buchanan (Box 79)
- Johnson, Charles E. (Box 29)
- Johnson, Charles E. (Engineering) (Box 132)
- Johnson, Charles E., Jr. (Box 29)
- Johnson, Cranford (Box 29)
- Johnson, Edward Anthony (Box 132)
- Johnson, Edward Anthony (Box 79)
- Johnson, F. Ross (Box 132)
- Johnson, F. Ross, Trustee 1987-, Trustee (Box 116)
- Johnson, Frank L. (Box 29)
- Johnson, Franklin P. (Box 29)
- Johnson, G. Allan (Box 79)
- Johnson, Gordon Lee (Box 29)
- Johnson, Harry W. (Box 79)
- Johnson, Jeff D. (Box 132)
- Johnson, Jeff D., d. 6/1960, Trustee (Box 116)
- Johnson, Joseph Carlton, II (Box 132)
- Johnson, Joseph Carlton, II (Box 79)
- Johnson, Kristina (Box 79)
- Johnson, Lawrence E. (Box 29)
- Johnson, Mychyle W. (Box 132)
- Johnson, Mychyle W. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Zoology, died/9/25/1950
- Johnson, Simon (Box 79)
- Johnson, Terry W. (Box 29)
- Johnson, Terry Walter, Jr. (Box 132)
- Johnson, Terry Walter, Jr. (Box 79)
- Johnson, Thomas Charles (Box 132)
- Johnson, Thomas Charles (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geology; Duke / UNC Oceanographic Consortium, Beaufort Marine Lab
- Johnson, Valen (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Institute of Stats and Decision Sciences
- Johnsrude, Irwin S. (Box 29)
- Johnston, Christopher (Box 29)
- Johnston, John D., Jr. (Box 132)
- Johnston, John D., Jr. (Box 151)
- Johnston, John D., Jr. (Box 79)
- Johnston, John Devereaux, Jr. (Box 29)
- Johnston, Lemuel Roy (Box 29)
- Johnston, Stephen Albert (Box 79)
- Johnston, William W. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology; Cytopathology and Cytogenics
- Joines, William Thomas (Box 132)
- Joines, William Thomas (Box 79)
- Joklik, Wolfgang Karl (Box 132)
- Joklik, Wolfgang Karl (Box 79)
- Jollis, James (Box 79)
- Jones, (Sara) Elizabeth (Box 29)
- Jones, Alex (Box 79)
- Jones, Barney (Box 79)
- Jones, Barney Lee (Box 132)
- Jones, Buford (Box 79)
- Jones, Claudius Parks (Box 29)
- Jones, Claudius Parks (Box 132)
- Jones, E. L., Sr., Trustee (Box 116)
- Jones, Edward E. (Box 132)
- Jones, Edward Ellsworth (Box 151)
- Jones, Edward Ellsworth (Box 79)
- Jones, Edwin L. (Box 132)
- Jones, Edwin L., Jr., Trustee (Box 116)
- Jones, Ellen (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: DUMC, 1999
- Jones, Evan (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: M and M Program, 2000
- Jones, Hunter (Box 29)
- Jones, J. David (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pediatrics / Psychiatric Liason
- Jones, Jameson (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School, died 7/18/1982
- Jones, L. Gregory "Greg" (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School, Effective 7/1/1997
- Jones, Oliver W. (Box 29)
- Jones, Paul (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Horticulturist, Duke Gardnes
- Jones, Philip L. (Box 79)
- Jones, Robert Howard (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Surgery; Radiology
- Jones, Robert R., Jr. (Box 29)
- Jones, Robert Randolph, Jr. (Box 132)
- Jones, Thomas T. (Box 29)
- Jones, Trina (Box 79)
- Jordan, A.C. (Box 151)
- Jordan, Archibald Currie (Box 29)
- Jordan, B. Everett (Box 132)
- Jordan, B. Everett (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; U.S. Senator
- Jordan, B. Everett [University Trustee, Alumnus], d. 3/1974 (Box 116)
- Jordan, Brady R. (Box 132)
- Jordan, Brady R. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Romance Languages, Retired 1960
- Jordan, Brady Rimbey (Box 29)
- Jordan, Charles E., 2 folders (Box 29)
- Jordan, Charles Edward (Box 132)
- Jordan, Charles Edward (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Public Relations, died/ 2/1974
- Jordan, Charlie (Box 151)
- Jordan, Henry W. (Box 113)
- Jordan, Lemuel R. (Box 30)
- Jordan, Lemuel Russell (Box 132)
- Jordan, Robert W. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; U.S. Ambassador to Saudi Arabia
- Jowell, Paul Simon (Box 79)
- Joyce, Kathleen M. (Box 79)
- Joyner, George W. (Box 30)
- Judd, Mary (Box 30)
- Judd, Walter H. (Box 132)
- Judd, Walter H. [Commencement Speaker], 1949, Trustee (Box 116)
- Kabala, Zbigniew J. (Box 79)
- Kadir, Saadoon (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiology; Interventional and Vascular Radiology
- Kahler, Stephen G. (Box 79)
- Kahr, Toby Y. (Box 79)
- Kaiser, Helen (Box 30)
- Kaiser, Helen (Box 151)
- Kaiwar, Vasant (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: History, 2001
- Kalat, James (Box 30)
- Kalbach, Constance (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sr. Research Scientist, Physics
- Kale, William A. (Box 30)
- Kalke, William C. (Box 79)
- Kalke, William C. (Box 151)
- Kamakura, Wagner A. (Box 79)
- Kamin, Henry (Box 30)
- Kamin, Henry (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biochemistry, Medicine
- Kammerer, Charlene (Box 30)
- Kammerer, Charlene (Box 132)
- Kandt, Raymond S. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurology, Pediatrics
- Kane, William J. (Box 30)
- Kanfer, Julian N. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurology and of Biochemistry
- Kantner, G.B. (Box 151)
- Kantner, George (Box 30)
- Kantner, George B. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Personnel DUMC
- Kao, Ming-Yang (Box 79)
- Kao, Tien-Cheng (Box 30)
- Kao, Tien-Cheng (Box 132)
- Kaplan, Alice Yaeger (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Romance Languages (French)
- Kapoor, Shankar Nath (Box 30)
- Karis, Joannes H. (Box 79)
- Karson, Jeffrey A. (Box 79)
- Karwan, Kirk (Box 30)
- Kasischke, Eric (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Research NSOE
- Kattan, Nicholas (Box 30)
- Katul, Gabriel G. "Gaby" (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Hydrology, NSOE
- Katz, David (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biomedical Engineering, Pratt
- Katz, Lawrence C. (Box 79)
- Katz, Samuel L. (Box 79)
- Katzenmeyer, William G. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Gradied School; Education
- Kaufman, Bernard (Box 79)
- Kaufman, Nathan (Box 30)
- Kaufman, Nathan (Box 151)
- Kaufman, Nathan (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology, DUMC
- Kaufman, Russell (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Education and Academic Affairs
- Kaufman, Wallace V. (Box 30)
- Kavass, Igor Ivar (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law; Law Library
- Kay, Helen (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Obstetrician, Maternal and Fetal Medied, Obstetrics and Gynecology
- Kay, Richard Frederick (Box 79)
- Keane, William M. (Box 30)
- Keane, William M. (Box 132)
- Kearney, Robert N. (Box 30)
- Kearns, Amos Ragan (Box 132)
- Kearns, Amos Ragan (Box 151)
- Kearns, Amos Ragan, d. 7/1979, Trustee (Box 116)
- Kearns, Nancy Jean (Box 30)
- Kearns, Ned S. (Box 30)
- Kearns, Ned S. (Box 132)
- Kedem, Gershon (Box 79)
- Keech, James M. (Box 30)
- Keech, James Maynard (Box 132)
- Keefe, Francis J., Jr. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medical Psychology; Pain Management Program
- Keefe, Richard S. E. (Box 79)
- Keene, Jack (Box 79)
- Keese, Peter G. (Box 30)
- Keese, Peter G. (Box 132)
- Keever, Catherine (Box 30)
- Keever, Catherine (Box 132)
- Keith, Charles Rush (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Child Psychology
- Keller, Catherine (Box 30)
- Keller, Kevin Lane (Box 79)
- Keller, Thomas Franklin (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Business Administration; Fuqua
- Kelley, Allen C. (Box 79)
- Kelley, Anthony (Box 79)
- Kelley, James M, Jr. (Box 30)
- Kelley, William H. (Box 30)
- Kelley, William N. (Box 30)
- Kelly, Susan (Box 113)
- Kelsoe, Garnett (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Immunology, 2001
- Kelvin, Frederick Maxwell (Box 30)
- Kemp, Edward H. (Box 30)
- Kempner, Walter (Box 30)
- Kempner, Walter (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Rice Diet Founder; Medicine
- Kempner, Walter (Box 151)
- Kenan, Patrick D. (Box 79)
- Kendall, Helen Mildred (Box 79)
- Keniston, Hayward (Box 30)
- Keniston, Hayward (Box 132)
- Kennedy, Fronde (Box 30)
- Kennedy, Fronde (Box 151)
- Kennedy, James S. (Box 30)
- Kenney, Philip E. (Box 30)
- Kenyon, Van L., Jr. (Box 30)
- Kenyon, Van Leslie, Jr. (Box 79)
- Keohane, Nannerl (Box 132)
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University - Biographical Sketch
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University - Education File
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University - Presidential Announcement
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University - Speeches
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 1985-1992
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 1993
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 1994
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 1995
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 1996
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 1997
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 1998
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 1999
- Keohane, Nannerl O. (Box 114)
  Biographical information. 8th President of Duke University, 2000-
- Keohane, Robert O. (Box 132)
- Keohane, Robert O. (Box 79)
- Keppel-Jones, Arthur Mervyn (Box 30)
- Keppel-Jones, Arthur Mervyn (Box 132)
- Kerby, Grace P. (Box 30)
- Kerby, Grace P. (Box 132)
- Kerby, Grace P. (Box 151)
- Kerckhoff, Alan C. (Box 79)
- Kerckhoff, Alan C. (Box 151)
- Kerr, RobertB. (Box 79)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Electrical Engineering, Effective 1/1/1991
- Ketterer, Stephen (Box 30)
- Keyssar, Alexander (Box 79)
- Khoury, Maroon B. (Box 30)
- Kiehart, Daniel P. (Box 80)
- Kiernan, Eileen Dorothy (Box 30)
- Kiernan, Eileen Dorothy (Box 132)
- Kilburn, Kaye Hatch (Box 30)
- Kilburn, S. Collins (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; Divinity School
- Kilgo, John C. (Box 30)
- Kilgo, John Carlisle (Box 80)
- Killiam, Allen P. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Obstetrics; Perinatology
- Killian, James Rhyne, Jr. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; President, MIT
- Killian, Keith (Box 80)
- Killian, Thomas J. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Scientist, Office of Ordinance Research
- Kilpatrick, Wylie (Box 30)
- Kilts, Clinton D. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry; Pharmacology
- Kimball, Gregory A. (Box 80)
- Kimble, Gregory Adams (Box 30)
- Kimble, Gregory Adams (Box 132)
- Kimm, Y. S. (Box 80)
- King, Andrew P. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Research Psychology
- King, Burton B. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Speech and Hearing Disorders, Surgery
- King, Charles Herschel (Box 30)
- King, Jack (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Communications Fuqua
- King, John B. (Box 30)
- King, John B. (Box 132)
- King, Joseph Edward (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Research in Anatomy
- King, Susan (Box 132)
- King, Susan, Trustee 1987, Trustee (Box 116)
- King, William Eskridge (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Founding University Archivist
- Kingsbury, William Benedict (Box 80)
- Kinkead, Duncan T. (Box 30)
- Kinney, Thomas (Box 30)
- Kinney, Thomas (Box 132)
- Kinney, Thomas R. (Box 80)
- Kinross-Wright, Vernon (Box 30)
- Kinross-Wright, Vernon (Box 80)
- Kinsborne, Marcel (Box 80)
- Kipnis, David M. (Box 30)
- Kirby, Wallace (Box 132)
- Kirby, Wallace, Trustee (Box 116)
- Kirk, John Franklin [University Trustee, Alumnus], Trustee (Box 116)
- Kirk, Ralph Gary (Box 30)
- Kirkendale, Ursula (Box 80)
- Kirkendale, Warren (Box 30)
- Kirkland, Kathryn B. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine/ Infectious Diseases
- Kirkland, Rebecca Trent, Trustee 1995-2001 (Box 116)
- Kirkland, W. H. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Plant Accounting
- Kirkwood, Marion R. (Box 30)
- Kirkwood, Marion R. (Box 132)
- Kirschner, Norman (Box 151)
- Kirschner, Norman (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pharmacology, Biochemestry
- Kirton, Brenda (Box 80)
- Kiser, J. J., Trustee to 2001 (Box 116)
- Kishnani, Priya S. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Med Gen, Peds
- Kiss, Elizabeth (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Kenan Ethics Program
- Kisslo, Joseph A. (Box 80)
- Kistler, Phil (Box 30)
- Kitchen, Joseph W., Jr (Box 80)
- Kitchen, Joseph W., Jr (and Dorothy) (Box 80)
- Kitschelt, Herbert (Box 80)
- Kiwanuka, Matia S.M. (Box 30)
- Klabes, Gunter (Box 30)
- Klassen, Preston (Box 80)
- Klause, Joseph Edward (Box 30)
- Klavins, Janis (Box 30)
- Klavins, Janis (Box 80)
- Klayman, Larry (Box 113)
- Klein, Dolph (Box 80)
- Klein, Emily (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geology Department
- Klein, James Raymond (Box 30)
- Klein, Robert F. (Box 30)
- Klein, Theodore George (Box 30)
- Klein, Theodore George (Box 151)
- Kleiner, Jillian A. (Box 80)
- Klenz, William (Box 30)
- Klenz, William (Box 132)
- Kliger, Samuel (Box 80)
- Kline, John (Box 30)
- Klintworth, Gordon Kenneth (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology, Opthamology
- Klopfer, Peter H. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Zoology, Post-1980
- Klopfer, Peter H. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Zoology, Pre-1980
- Klopfer, Walter George (Box 30)
- Klotman, Paul E. (Box 80)
- Knight, Conrad Merton (Box 80)
- Knight, Douglas M., 9 folders (Box 31)
- Knight, Douglas M., 2 folders (Box 32)
- Knight, Douglas M. (Box 80)
- Knight, Douglas M. (Box 133)
- Knight, Robert, Jr. (Box 32)
- Knight, Robert, Jr. (Box 133)
- Knight, Robert, Jr. (Box 151)
- Knight, W.D. (Box 32)
- Knisley, William Hagerman (Box 32)
- Knisley, William Hagerman (Box 133)
- Knoerr, Kenneth R. (Box 80)
- Knops, Frederick W., Jr. (Box 133)
- Knowles, John Hilton, d. 3/1978, Trustee (Box 116)
- Knox, (Mrs.) Ellen Matteson (Box 32)
- Knox, Edward M., Jr. (Box 32)
- Knox, Paul R. (Box 32)
- Koch, Ruth M. (Box 32)
- Koch, Sigmund (Box 32)
- Koch, Sigmund (Box 133)
- Koch, Sigmund (Box 151)
- Koch, Walter J. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Experimental Surgery
- Koenig, Harold G. (Box 133)
- Koenig, Harold G. (Box 80)
- Koenig, J. Frank (Box 32)
- Koepke, John A. (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Hospital Labs
- Koesy, Sheldon Fred (Box 32)
- Kofodimos, Joan (Box 80)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Organizational Behavior
- Kohler, Ivo (Box 32)
- Kohn, Carol L. A., Trustee (Box 116)
- Kohn, Henry I. (Box 32)
- Kohn, Michael C. (Box 80)
- Kohorn, Bruce (Box 80)
- Koller, Elizabeth A. (Box 80)
- Kolotkin, Roneet L. (Box 80)